- Miss Dionne Warwick.
(audience applauds and cheers)
(bright music)
♪ The moment I wake up ♪
♪ Before I put on my makeup ♪
♪ I say a little
prayer for you ♪
♪ While combing my hair now ♪
♪ And wondering what
dress to wear now ♪
♪ I say a little
prayer for you ♪
♪ Forever, forever,
you'll stay in my heart ♪
♪ And I will love you ♪
♪ Forever, and ever,
we never will part ♪
♪ Oh, how I'll love you ♪
♪ Together, together,
that's how it must be ♪
♪ To live without you ♪
♪ Would only mean
heartbreak for me ♪
♪ I run for the bus, dear ♪
♪ And while riding I
think of us, dear ♪
♪ I say a little
prayer for you ♪
♪ At work I just take time ♪
♪ And all through my
coffee break-time ♪
♪ I say a little
prayer for you ♪
♪ Forever, forever,
you'll stay in my heart ♪
♪ And I will love you ♪
♪ Forever, and ever,
we never will part ♪
♪ Oh, how I'll love you ♪
♪ Together, together,
that's how it must be ♪
♪ To live without you ♪
♪ Would only mean
heartbreak for me ♪
(scatting)
♪ I say a little
prayer for you ♪
(scatting)
♪ I say a little
prayer for you ♪
♪ Forever, forever,
you'll stay in my heart ♪
♪ And I will love you ♪
♪ Forever, and ever,
we never will part ♪
♪ Oh, how I'll love you ♪
♪ Together, together,
that's how it must be ♪
♪ To live without you ♪
♪ Would only mean
heartbreak for me ♪
♪ My darling believe me ♪
♪ For me there is no one ♪
♪ But you ♪
♪ Please love me too ♪
♪ I'm in love with you ♪
♪ Answer my prayer ♪
♪ Say you love me too ♪
♪ Why don't you answer
my prayer, yeah ♪
♪ You know that every day
I say a little prayer ♪
(audience applauds and cheers)
Thank you!